[Being A Hero]
[كونك بطل]
[Episode 11]
[الحلقة 11]
[Counter Narcotics Detachment]
[مفرزة مكافحة المخدرات]
A cloned car?
سيارة مستنسخة؟
As long as they change the car plate,
طالما أنهم يغيرون لوحة السيارة ،
there's no way we can find them.
لا توجد طريقة يمكننا العثور عليها.
We're running out of time.
نحن نفاد الوقت.
Whatever.
ايا كان.
What about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
We will find information about all cars
سنجد معلومات حول جميع السيارات
of the same model,
من نفس النموذج ،
regardless of their car plate numbers.
بغض النظر عن أرقام لوحات سيارتهم.
Let's do this.
هيا بنا نقوم بذلك.
How do we do this?
كيف نفعل ذلك؟
It's as if looking for a needle in a haystack.
يبدو الأمر كما لو كنت تبحث عن إبرة في كومة قش.
We have to do it anyway.
علينا أن نفعل ذلك على أي حال.
Come on.
هيا.
I've investigated
لقد حققت
He Jiashu's social relations
علاقات جياشو الاجتماعية
and verified it with the social worker.
والتحقق منها مع الأخصائي الاجتماعي.
This was the guy
كان هذا هو الرجل
who took He Jiashu's mom.
الذي أخذ والدة هو جياشو.
His name is Jiang Yu.
اسمه جيانغ يو.
[Personal profile] He's from Yunhe
[الملف الشخصي] إنه من Yunhe
and is unemployed.
وهو عاطل عن العمل.
Will this help?
هل سيساعد هذا؟
I'll try.
سأحاول.
Keep yourself awake.
ابق نفسك مستيقظا.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
I found it.
لقد وجدتها.
After they left the nursing home,
بعد مغادرتهم دار المسنين ،
they got themselves a new car plate.
لقد حصلوا على لوحة سيارة جديدة لأنفسهم.
[2019-09-02, Monday, Cang F·FU829] That was why we couldn't find it.
[2019-09-02 ، الاثنين ، Cang F · FU829] لهذا السبب لم نتمكن من العثور عليه.
He was quite cunning.
كان ماكرًا جدًا.
What about the route?
ماذا عن الطريق؟
The route he took.
الطريق الذي سلكه.
Qiang.
تشيانغ.
Can you tell Chief Liu
هل يمكنك إخبار الرئيس ليو
to send us a SWAT team to back us up?
لترسل لنا فريق SWAT لدعمنا؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Are you really going to bear everything yourself?
هل ستتحمل كل شيء بنفسك حقًا؟
When they took your mom with them,
عندما أخذوا والدتك معهم ،
they didn't take her medication along.
لم يأخذوا الدواء معها.
I suppose you know your mom's health condition
أفترض أنك تعرف حالة والدتك الصحية
way better than we do.
طريقة أفضل مما نفعل.
You need to save my mom.
أنت بحاجة لإنقاذ أمي.
Please, save my mom.
من فضلك ، احفظ أمي.
Wu Gang, the father of Wu Zhenfeng.
وو قانغ والد وو تشن فنغ.
Do you know him?
هل تعرفه؟
Please, save my mom.
من فضلك ، احفظ أمي.
June 2016.
يونيو 2016.
Your mom underwent a kidney transplant surgery.
خضعت والدتك لعملية زرع الكلى.
According to what we know,
حسب ما نعرفه
you were desperate to raise funds for her medical bill
كنت في حاجة ماسة لجمع الأموال لفاتورتها الطبية
and gambled all the money you borrowed
وراهن بكل الأموال التي اقترضتها
at the casino.
في الكازينو.
In the end, you lost all your stake.
في النهاية ، فقدت كل حصصك.
It was Wu Gang who settled the debt for you
لقد كان وو جانج هو الذي سدد الدين نيابة عنك
and gave you 100,000 yuan afterward.
وأعطاك 100000 يوان بعد ذلك.
After what happened to Wu Gang,
بعد ما حدث لـ Wu Gang ،
not only did you pay off
لم تسدد ثمارها فقط
all your debts,
كل ديونك ،
but you also managed to pay
لكنك تمكنت أيضًا من الدفع
for your mom's kidney transplant surgery.
لجراحة زرع الكلى لأمك.
Tell me now.
أخبرني الآن.
Where did you get all the money?
من أين لك كل المال؟
Save my mom, please.
حفظ أمي من فضلك.
It was your boss who was trying to kill me
كان رئيسك هو الذي كان يحاول قتلي
together with you, right?
معكم صحيح؟
Wu Gang helped you
ساعدك وو قانغ
when you were in dire need of help.
عندما كنت في حاجة ماسة للمساعدة.
On the other hand,
من ناحية أخرى،
your boss only paid you when he needed you.
رئيسك في العمل يدفع لك فقط عندما يحتاجك.
When you're in trouble,
عندما تكون في ورطة ،
he took your mom hostage, trying to blackmail you.
لقد أخذ والدتك رهينة في محاولة لابتزازك.
For every second
لكل ثانية
you're wasting now,
أنت تضيع الآن ،
your mom
والدتك
is one step closer to death.
على بعد خطوة واحدة من الموت.
Tell me
أخبرني
who you're working for!
لمن تعمل!
Save my mom!
حفظ أمي!
Save my mom first!
حفظ أمي أولا!
If you don't save my mom,
إذا لم تنقذ أمي ،
I won't tell you anything.
لن أخبرك بأي شيء.
Save my mom now!
حفظ أمي الآن!
Let's go.
لنذهب.
The weather is too hot.
الجو حار جدا.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
It's extremely humid too.
إنه رطب للغاية أيضًا.
How did the poker game go yesterday?
كيف سارت لعبة البوكر أمس؟
I won some money.
فزت ببعض المال.
Let's play again in a few days.
لنلعب مرة أخرى في غضون أيام قليلة.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
-Police. Stay still! -Stay still!
-شرطة.  اثبت مكانك!  -اثبت مكانك!
Stay still!
اثبت مكانك!
Stop moving.
توقف عن الحركة.
Get down and put your hands on the back of your head.
انزل وضع يديك على مؤخرة رأسك.
Shu is our debtor.
شو هو مديننا.
Yesterday...
في الامس...
We haven't been able to
لم نتمكن من ذلك
get in touch with him since yesterday.
تواصل معه منذ البارحة.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Qiang.
تشيانغ.
Call the ambulance.
استدعاء سيارة الإسعاف.
Send her to the hospital.
أرسلها إلى المستشفى.
We didn't do anything to her.
لم نفعل أي شيء لها.
Tell me now.
أخبرني الآن.
They rescued her?
أنقذوها؟
What a useless bunch.
يا لها من حفنة عديمة الفائدة.
How could you let them take her?
كيف يمكنك السماح لهم بأخذها؟
How many times have I told you this?
كم مرة قلت لك هذا؟
Always stay on your toes.
ابق دائمًا على أصابع قدميك.
You only had to change to another car halfway through the journey.
كان عليك فقط التغيير إلى سيارة أخرى في منتصف الطريق خلال الرحلة.
Donkeys.
الحمير.
Are you?
أنت؟
I don't know what to do now.
أنا لا أعرف ماذا أفعل الآن.
I can't do anything about it.
لا يمكنني فعل أي شيء حيال ذلك.
You need to figure it out yourself.
أنت بحاجة لمعرفة ذلك بنفسك.
What a useless bunch.
يا لها من حفنة عديمة الفائدة.
Mr. Wan.
السيد وان.
The police
الشرطة
took Shu's mom.
تولى والدة شو.
I didn't expect the police to be this efficient.
لم أكن أتوقع أن تكون الشرطة بهذه الكفاءة.
Shu's mom was taken hostage.
تم أخذ والدة شو كرهينة.
Shu will rat you out
شو سوف يرفع لك
very soon.
قريبا جدا.
He won't.
لن يفعل.
We're good friends.
نحن صديقان حميمان.
He's been working for me for years.
لقد كان يعمل لدي لسنوات.
I am sure that he will never betray me.
أنا متأكد من أنه لن يخونني أبدًا.
Hey. Yang Yi.
يا.  يانغ يي.
Chen Yu.
تشن يو.
We've rescued
لقد أنقذنا
He Jiashu's mom.
والدة جياشو.
We've sent her to the hospital.
لقد أرسلناها إلى المستشفى.
Everything went well.
كل شيء سار بشكل جيد.
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
How's everything at your end?
كيف هو كل شيء في نهايتك؟
I'm questioning him.
أنا أستجوبه.
Pass the phone to He Jiashu.
مرر الهاتف إلى He Jiashu.
His mom wants to talk to him.
والدته تريد التحدث معه.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Jiashu.
جياشو.
Talk to the police.
تحدث إلى الشرطة.
I'll be waiting for you at home.
سأكون في انتظارك في المنزل.
Yang Yi.
يانغ يي.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
Please take good care of her.
من فضلك اعتني بها جيدا
We'll resume our questioning.
سنستأنف استجوابنا.
Can you talk to us now?
هل يمكنك التحدث إلينا الآن؟
Shu's mom got rescued,
تم إنقاذ والدة شو ،
and Dong...
ودونغ ...
It seems like
انها تبدو مثل
Shu doesn't know who Hao Dong is.
شو لا يعرف من هو هاو دونغ.
With your relationship,
مع علاقتك ،
do you really have to be this nervous about it?
هل حقا يجب أن تكون متوترا بهذا الشكل؟
Mr. Wan.
السيد وان.
You know how Dong is.
أنت تعرف كيف هو دونغ.
He is always brutal and merciless
إنه دائمًا وحشي ولا يرحم
when it comes to business.
عندما يتعلق الأمر بالأعمال.
Whenever his subordinates
كلما مرؤوسوه
makes a mistake, no matter how small it is,
يرتكب خطأ مهما كان صغيرا ،
he will get rid of them immediately.
سوف يتخلص منهم على الفور.
Never let Dong find out
لا تدع دونغ يكتشف ذلك
that Shu's mom has been rescued.
أن والدة شو تم إنقاذها.
Can you do me a favor?
هل يمكنك أن تسدي لي خدمة؟
Can you?
هل تستطيع؟
Who brought the police
الذي أحضر الشرطة
to the boxing casino
إلى كازينو الملاكمة
that day?
ذلك اليوم؟
Wu Zhenfeng.
وو تشن فنغ.
Who brought the police
الذي أحضر الشرطة
to the boxing casino
إلى كازينو الملاكمة
that day?
ذلك اليوم؟
It was Wu Zhenfeng, Mr. Wan.
كان وو Zhenfeng ، السيد وان.
You should go.
يجب أن تذهب.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Who are you working for?
لصالح من تعمل؟
Hu Qingshan.
هو تشينغشان.
Are you trying to fool me?
هل تحاول خداعى؟
Putting the blame on a dead man, huh?
إلقاء اللوم على رجل ميت ، أليس كذلك؟
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
Three years ago,
منذ ثلاثة أعوام،
soon after Wu Gang gave me the money,
بعد فترة وجيزة من إعطائي وو جانج المال ،
Hu Qingshan approached me.
اقترب مني هو تشينغشان.
(He said that Wu Gang reported his boss to the police,)
(قال إن وو جانج أبلغ الشرطة برئيسه ،)
(and he wanted to take revenge on him.)
(وأراد أن ينتقم منه).
Here's a million.
هنا مليون.
Get your mom a new kidney
احصل على كلية جديدة لأمك
as soon as possible.
في أقرب وقت ممكن.
Kun,
متي،
this is not right.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
I can't take this.
لا أستطيع أخذ هذا.
You're not getting the money for free.
أنت لا تحصل على المال مجانًا.
You work for Wu Gang, right?
أنت تعمل لدى وو جانج ، أليس كذلك؟
Do me a favor.
أعمل لي معروفا.
(Then,)
(ثم،)
(you helped Hu Qingshan)
(لقد ساعدت Hu Qingshan)
(plant the drugs in Wu Gang's car.)
(زرع الأدوية في سيارة وو جانج).
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
Wu Gang helped you settle your debt
ساعدك Wu Gang في تسوية ديونك
and gave you money.
وأعطاك المال.
You took his money,
أخذت ماله ،
but you framed him.
لكنك قمت بتأطيره.
100,000 yuan
100000 يوان
wasn't enough to save my mom.
لم يكن كافيًا لإنقاذ أمي.
My mom was at death's door.
كانت أمي على باب الموت.
After that incident,
بعد تلك الحادثة ،
you became a member of K.
أصبحت عضوًا في K.
I didn't.
لم أكن.
Hu Qingshan
هو تشينغشان
only put me in charge of the boxing casino,
فقط اجعلني مسؤولاً عن كازينو الملاكمة ،
so that I could earn some small money
حتى أتمكن من كسب بعض المال الصغير
to pay my mom's medical bills.
لدفع الفواتير الطبية لأمي.
That is everything I know.
هذا كل ما أعرفه.
K only asks for one thing.
يسأل K عن شيء واحد فقط.
He wants Hai
يريد هاي
to be in charge of sending out K's goods
ليكون مسؤولاً عن إرسال بضائع K.
from my boxing casino.
من كازينو الملاكمة الخاص بي.
You're lying.
انت تكذب.
Hu Qingshan betrayed K
قام Hu Qingshan بخيانة K.
a year ago.
قبل عام.
Why would K keep you around
لماذا سيبقيك K حولك
and let you be in charge
وتتيح لك أن تكون مسؤولاً
of such an important place?
لمثل هذا المكان المهم؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Who are you working for?
لصالح من تعمل؟
Sir.
سيد.
Please stop pushing me.
من فضلك توقف عن دفعني.
I've told you everything I could.
لقد أخبرتك بكل ما أستطيع.
Do you really wish to see me dead?
هل تريد حقا أن تراني ميتا؟
They took your mom hostage.
لقد أخذوا والدتك رهينة.
Do you really think
هل تعتقد حقا
you can bear everything yourself?
يمكنك تحمل كل شيء بنفسك؟
Tell you what.
اخبرك بماذا.
None of them out there
لا أحد منهم هناك
wishes to see you alive.
تتمنى رؤيتك حيا.
The memory card is full.
بطاقة الذاكرة ممتلئة.
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
I'll get it changed.
سوف أتغير.
Sir.
سيد.
You were really lucky
كنت حقا محظوظا
that I didn't kill you three years ago.
أنني لم أقتلك قبل ثلاث سنوات.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Stop the investigation.
أوقف التحقيق.
To be honest with you,
أن نكون صادقين معك،
even if I tell you who I'm working for,
حتى لو أخبرتك بمن أعمل ،
you won't be able to do anything about it.
لن تكون قادرًا على فعل أي شيء حيال ذلك.
What's that supposed to mean?
ما الذي يفترض أن يعني؟
Tell me now!
أخبرني الآن!
Your chief is Liu, isn't he?
رئيسك هو ليو ، أليس كذلك؟
Go and ask around.
اذهب واسأل من حولك.
He has a nephew,
لديه ابن أخ ،
and that guy is who I'm working for.
وهذا الرجل هو الذي أعمل لديه.
How do you plan to keep working on this case?
كيف تخطط لمواصلة العمل في هذه القضية؟
[Mixiang]
[ميكسيانج]
[Three years ago, He Jiashu]
[قبل ثلاث سنوات ، هو جياشو]
[Director Lin]
[المخرج لين]
Where is Hao Dong?
أين هاو دونغ؟
Something happened to the boxing casino.
حدث شيء ما لكازينو الملاكمة.
Was Hao Dong
هل كان هاو دونغ
trying to kill Wu Zhenfeng?
تحاول قتل وو Zhenfeng؟
Look at you guys.
انظروا إليكم يا رفاق.
You are young
انت صغير السن
and reckless.
ومتهور.
We have to kill him.
علينا قتله.
We underestimated him.
قللنا من شأنه.
Lei.
لي.
Mind your words.
مانع كلامك.
You're too inexperienced.
أنت عديم الخبرة للغاية.
What do you know?
ماذا تعرف؟
Do we really have to kill someone?
هل حقا علينا قتل شخص ما؟
Hu Qingshan is dead.
مات هو تشينغشان.
So is Li Zhengqiang.
هكذا هو Li Zhengqiang.
How many more men are you going to kill
كم عدد الرجال الذين ستقتلهم
before you'll put an end to this?
قبل أن تضع حدا لهذا؟
I didn't kill the two of them.
لم أقتل الاثنين.
But Hao Dong
لكن هاو دونغ
was the one who killed Li Zhengqiang, right?
هل كان الشخص الذي قتل Li Zhengqiang ، أليس كذلك؟
Dong.
دونغ.
Who did I kill, Mr. Wan?
من قتلت يا سيد وان؟
Have a seat. Let's eat.
تفضل بالجلوس.  لنأكل.
Mr. Wan.
السيد وان.
I heard about what happened to the boxing casino.
سمعت عما حدث لكازينو الملاكمة.
Mengmeng brought a stranger there.
أحضر Mengmeng شخصًا غريبًا هناك.
Dong.
دونغ.
Wu Zhenfeng was the one
كان وو تشن فنغ هو الشخص
who brought the police to the boxing casino.
الذي أحضر الشرطة إلى كازينو الملاكمة.
Where is Mengmeng?
أين مينجمينج؟
Has she been released?
هل أطلق سراحها؟
Yes.
نعم.
She was a little frightened,
كانت خائفة قليلا ،
but she'll be fine after she gets some rest at home.
لكنها ستكون بخير بعد أن تحصل على قسط من الراحة في المنزل.
It's good to hear that she's fine.
من الجيد أن أسمع أنها بخير.
She's your only daughter.
إنها ابنتك الوحيدة.
You should take good care of her.
يجب أن تعتني بها جيدًا.
Dong,
دونغ ،
what should we do with Wu Zhenfeng?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل مع وو تشن فنغ؟
Wu Zhenfeng managed to leave the Public Security Bureau
تمكن Wu Zhenfeng من مغادرة مكتب الأمن العام
so soon.
قريبا جدا.
I'm sure there's something wrong going on.
أنا متأكد من أن هناك خطأ ما يحدث.
Dong.
دونغ.
Break his leg,
كسر ساقه،
and drop him in another country.
وإسقاطه في بلد آخر.
Mr. Wan said
قال السيد وان
that we shouldn't kill anyone.
أننا لا ينبغي أن نقتل أحدا.
Mr. Wan.
السيد وان.
Are you happy
هل أنت مسرور
with this arrangement?
بهذا الترتيب؟
[One week later]
[بعد اسبوع]
[Yunhe Detention Center]
[مركز احتجاز يونهي]
Lei. He's out.
لي.  غادر.
Follow him.
اتبعه.
[Tomb of Yang Mei and Wu Gang]
[قبر يانغ مي ووو غانغ]
Dad.
أب.
Mom.
أم.
You were buried at the same place.
لقد دفنت في نفس المكان.
How nice.
كم هو جميل.
I have not been able to drop by
لم أتمكن من المرور
in the past three years.
في السنوات الثلاث الماضية.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
But you're not all good either.
لكنك لست جيدًا أيضًا.
You didn't leave me
أنت لم تتركني
any clues at all.
أي أدلة على الإطلاق.
Do you know
هل تعرف
what the past three years have been like for me?
كيف كانت السنوات الثلاث الماضية بالنسبة لي؟
To prove your innocence,
لإثبات براءتك ،
I did
فعلتُ
everything I could,
كل ما بوسعي ،
but I really couldn't find any clues.
لكنني حقًا لم أجد أي أدلة.
I'm so tired.
أنا متعب جدا.
I don't know
لا أعرف
how long I can keep going.
إلى متى يمكنني الاستمرار.
Don't you think it's a little too late
ألا تعتقد أنه فات الأوان قليلاً
to visit your parents now?
لزيارة والديك الآن؟
Why did you lie to me?
لماذا كذبت علي؟
You did help me
لقد ساعدتني
bury them together.
ادفنهم معا.
I didn't do that to help you.
لم أفعل ذلك لمساعدتك.
When I was a kid,
عندما كنت طفلا،
your parents took really good care of me.
اهتم والديك بي جيدًا.
This is what I should do.
هذا ما يجب أن أفعله.
According to Huang Wenlin,
وفقا لهوانغ وينلين ،
you left Mengka and came back here
غادرت مينكا وعادت إلى هنا
so that you could make a deal with K.
حتى تتمكن من عقد صفقة مع K.
Li Shougui and Du Hai also said
وقال لي شوقوي ودو هاي أيضا
that you wanted to work with Shu.
أنك أردت العمل مع Shu.
Is there anything
هل يوجد أي شئ
you want to tell me?
تريد أن تقول لي؟
Uncle.
اخو الام.
Are you
أنت
at Nancheng Bus Stop?
في محطة حافلات نانتشنغ؟
My friend saw you there.
رآك صديقي هناك.
Before we have any solid evidence
قبل أن يكون لدينا أي دليل قوي
to prove
ليثبت
that your dad is innocent,
أن والدك بريء ،
we can't
لا نستطيع
exculpate him.
تبرئته.
(We will never)
(نحن لن)
(wrong a good man,)
(خطأ رجل طيب ،)
(but we'll also never)
(لكننا لن نفعل ذلك أبدًا)
(let a bad guy go.)
(دع الرجل السيئ يذهب.)
Do you think
هل تعتقد
my dad was good or bad?
كان والدي جيدًا أم سيئًا؟
I'm still trying to find out,
ما زلت أحاول اكتشاف ذلك ،
but all I've got so far are just some minor clues.
ولكن كل ما لدي حتى الآن هو مجرد بعض القرائن الثانوية.
I haven't managed to find any solid evidence.
لم أتمكن من العثور على أي دليل قوي.
I can't form
لا أستطيع تشكيل
a complete chain of evidence
سلسلة كاملة من الأدلة
to prove your dad's innocence yet.
لإثبات براءة والدك حتى الآن.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You must have visited them very frequently
لابد أنك قمت بزيارتهم كثيرًا
in the past three years.
في السنوات الثلاث الماضية.
How clean the tomb is.
كم هو نظيف القبر.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
Wu Zhenfeng.
وو تشن فنغ.
I know you want to avenge your parents' death,
أعلم أنك تريد الانتقام لموت والديك ،
but you're in grave danger
لكنك في خطر شديد
because you're getting more and more extreme.
لأنك تزداد تطرفا.
You need us to help you.
تحتاج منا لمساعدتك.
Stop working on this.
توقف عن العمل على هذا.
The longer the investigation goes on,
كلما طالت مدة التحقيق ،
the more dangerous it is for you.
كلما كان الأمر أكثر خطورة بالنسبة لك.
Over the past three years,
على مدى السنوات الثلاث الماضية ،
I've learned that the closer you get to the truth,
تعلمت أنه كلما اقتربت من الحقيقة ،
the more dangerous it will get.
ستصبح أكثر خطورة.
Exactly because it's dangerous,
بالضبط لأنه خطير ،
you need our help even more.
أنت بحاجة إلى مساعدتنا أكثر.
You...
أنت...
Are you sure
هل أنت واثق
there's nothing wrong with your team?
لا حرج في فريقك؟
Lei.
لي.
I'm at the cemetery.
أنا في المقبرة.
There's someone beside him.
هناك شخص ما بجانبه.
It's the policeman, Chen Yu.
إنه الشرطي ، تشين يو.
Don't do anything there.
لا تفعل أي شيء هناك.
Keep following them.
استمر في متابعتهم.
Got it.
فهمتك.
I'm sure Dong is trying to figure out a way
أنا متأكد من أن دونغ يحاول اكتشاف طريقة
to get rid of us.
للتخلص منا.
Dong is a very powerful man at Yunhe.
دونغ رجل قوي جدا في Yunhe.
Feng.
فنغ.
What are you actually planning to do?
ما الذي تخطط لفعله بالفعل؟
I've asked you the same questions many times,
لقد طرحت عليك نفس الأسئلة عدة مرات ،
but you never told me anything.
لكنك لم تخبرني بأي شيء.
You are making me
أنت تصنعني
really nervous.
عصبية حقا.
From now on, you'll just do whatever I say.
من الآن فصاعدًا ، ستفعل كل ما أقوله.
You only have to enjoy life
ما عليك سوى الاستمتاع بالحياة
and worry about nothing else.
ولا تقلق بشأن أي شيء آخر.
I came back to Yunhe
عدت إلى Yunhe
to be the Drug King.
ليكون ملك المخدرات.
Feng.
فنغ.
All of us
كلنا
will listen to you from now on.
سوف يستمع إليك من الآن فصاعدًا.
-Hui.
-هوى. -هوى.
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Feng!
فنغ!
Lei?
لي؟
Are you working for Dong?
هل تعمل لدى دونغ؟
Leave Yunhe now.
اترك يونهي الآن.
Dong will never see you.
لن يراك دونغ أبدا.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Feng.
فنغ.
Run, Feng.
اركض يا فنغ.
After them.
بعدهم.
Take the back alley.
اسلك الزقاق الخلفي.
Wu Zhenfeng.
وو تشن فنغ.
I'm telling you.
أنا أخبرك.
You won't be able to leave Yunhe
لن تكون قادرًا على مغادرة Yunhe
even if you kill me today.
حتى لو قتلتني اليوم.
Do it if you don't trust me.
افعل ذلك إذا كنت لا تثق بي.
Call Dong now.
اتصل بـ Dong الآن.
Do you want to talk to Dong?
هل تريد التحدث مع دونغ؟
Who do you think you are?
من تظن نفسك؟
Shu was working for you.
كان شو يعمل من أجلك.
You said that you kept his mom here,
قلت إنك أبقيت والدته هنا ،
yet the police took her away.
لكن الشرطة أخذتها بعيدًا.
What did you promise me?
ماذا وعدتني؟
Tell you what.
اخبرك بماذا.
The person he rats out has to be silenced.
يجب إسكات الشخص الذي يصرخ به.
This is the rule.
هذه هي القاعدة.
[Dong]
[دونغ]
[Lei]
[لي]
If you can't silence him,
إذا لم تستطع إسكاته ،
I'll make sure you never get to talk again.
سأحرص على عدم التحدث مرة أخرى.
Dong.
دونغ.
Lei is calling.
يتصل "لي".
Hey.
يا.
Dong.
دونغ.
Wu Zhenfeng.
وو تشن فنغ.
Wu Zhenfeng?
وو Zhenfeng؟
You did everything
لقد فعلت كل شيء
just to hide from me.
فقط للاختباء عني.
Are you scared of me?
هل انت خائف مني؟
Let Jiang Lei go,
دع جيانغ لي يذهب ،
and you can go back to Mengka alive.
ويمكنك العودة إلى Mengka حيا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
But before I leave,
لكن قبل أن أغادر ،
I'll hand this man
سأسلم هذا الرجل
to the police.
إلى الشرطة.
Just like what I did to the boxing casino.
تمامًا مثل ما فعلته في كازينو الملاكمة.
Wu Zhenfeng.
وو تشن فنغ.
Is that a threat?
هل هذا تهديد؟
Dong.
دونغ.
I'm very familiar
أنا مألوف جدا
with the Counter Narcotics Detachment.
مع مفرزة مكافحة المخدرات.
Do you want to bet?
هل تريد أن الرهان؟
Let's meet up, then.
فلنلتقي إذن.
Where did Wu Zhenfeng go?
أين ذهب وو تشن فنغ؟
It seems like the guy who hit us
يبدو أنه الرجل الذي ضربنا
kidnapped him.
خطفه.
Do you know the guy
هل تعرف الرجل
who kidnapped him?
من خطفه؟
I don't.
أنا لا.
Who do you think he is?
من تعتقد هو؟
Probably someone who works for Dong.
ربما شخص يعمل مع دونغ.
Dong?
دونغ؟
The guy in K.
الرجل في K.
Do you know Dong?
هل تعرف دونغ؟
I don't.
أنا لا.
Li Shougui.
لي شوقي.
Wu Zhenfeng went to the rehab center
ذهب Wu Zhenfeng إلى مركز إعادة التأهيل
to look for you, right?
للبحث عنك ، أليس كذلك؟
You brought him to the boxing casino too.
لقد أحضرته إلى كازينو الملاكمة أيضًا.
You were also the one who bought him all the boxing gear.
كنت أيضًا من اشتريت له كل أدوات الملاكمة.
Say it.
قلها.
Why did Wu Zhenfeng go to you?
لماذا ذهب Wu Zhenfeng إليك؟
When we were there,
عندما كنا هناك ،
Wu Zhenfeng told me
قال لي وو Zhenfeng
that he wanted to meet Dong.
أنه يريد مقابلة دونغ.
He wanted me to bring him to Dong.
أراد مني أن أحضره إلى دونغ.
But I don't know Dong personally.
لكني لا أعرف دونغ شخصيًا.
All I know is that he has a boxing casino.
كل ما أعرفه هو أن لديه كازينو ملاكمة.
He told me,
قال لي،
turn the boxing casino upside down
اقلب كازينو الملاكمة رأسًا على عقب
and Dong would go to him instead.
وسيذهب دونغ إليه بدلاً من ذلك.
Why was Wu Zhenfeng looking for Dong?
لماذا كان Wu Zhenfeng يبحث عن Dong؟
I have no idea.
ليس لدي أي فكرة.
By the way,
على فكرة،
when we were having lamb skewers,
عندما كان لدينا أسياخ لحم الضأن ،
Wu Zhenfeng said something
قال وو Zhenfeng شيئا
that threw me into fright.
دفعني إلى الرعب.
What did he say?
ماذا قال؟
He said he wanted to be the Drug King.
قال إنه يريد أن يكون ملك المخدرات.
Listen, Li Shougui.
استمع لي شوقي.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
you'll tell me
ستخبرني
everything Wu Zhenfeng does,
كل شيء يفعله Wu Zhenfeng ،
every person he meets,
كل شخص يقابله ،
and everything he says,
وكل ما يقوله ،
including those he says to you.
بما في ذلك من يقول لك.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
I'm telling you
أنا أخبرك
that we are very positive
أننا إيجابيون للغاية
that Wu Zhenfeng is involved in a drug crime.
أن Wu Zhenfeng متورط في جريمة مخدرات.
This is your chance,
هذه فرصتك
so don't tell me that you're not capable of doing it.
لذلك لا تخبرني أنك غير قادر على فعل ذلك.
I can do this.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك.
Hao Dong!
هاو دونغ!
Give it to me.
اعطني اياه.
The thing you got from your dad.
الشيء الذي حصلت عليه من والدك.
Don't blame me for showing no mercy.
لا تلومني لعدم إبداء أي رحمة.
Are you Dong?
هل انت دونغ؟
Whatever I didn't do three years ago,
كل ما لم أفعله قبل ثلاث سنوات ،
I'll do it today.
سأفعل ذلك اليوم.
Do it.
افعلها.
Don't come near me.
لا تقترب مني.
Dong.
دونغ.
Dong, wait.
دونغ ، انتظر.
It was Erliang who sent me here
كان إرليانغ هو من أرسلني إلى هنا
to make a deal with you.
لعقد صفقة معك.
Wait, Dong.
انتظر دونغ.
His uncle is a policeman.
عمه شرطي.
His uncle is a policeman!
عمه شرطي!
Trust me. I'll kill him.
صدقني.  سوف اقتله.
Wu Zhenfeng.
وو تشن فنغ.
You've got the wrong person.
لقد حصلت على الشخص الخطأ.
Do you want to make a deal with me?
هل تريد عقد صفقة معي؟
Let him go first.
دعه يذهب أولا.
Then we'll talk.
سنتكلم بعد ذلك.
Dong.
دونغ.
Don't you have any other tricks?
أليس لديك أي حيل أخرى؟
Erliang sent you here.
أرسلك إرليانغ إلى هنا.
Does Mengka have any other tricks?
هل لدى مينجكا أي حيل أخرى؟
Dong.
دونغ.
I trust you.
أنا أثق بك.
Bullshit.
هراء.
Even I don't trust myself.
حتى أنا لا أثق بنفسي.
How can you trust me?
كيف يمكنك الوثوق بي؟
[Wu Zhenfeng]
[وو زهينفنغ]
(Over the past three years,)
(على مدى السنوات الثلاث الماضية ،)
(I spent every day looking for clues)
(قضيت كل يوم أبحث عن أدلة)
(to I can avenge my dad.)
(لأستطيع الانتقام من والدي.)
(When I was at the boxing casino today)
(عندما كنت في كازينو الملاكمة اليوم)
(and saw the guy nicknamed Shu)
(ورأيت الرجل الملقب شو)
(for the first time,)
(لأول مرة،)
(do you know how I felt?)
(هل تعرف كيف شعرت؟)
(It was my first time)
(لقد كانت المرة الاولي لي)
(getting so close to the truth.)
(الاقتراب من الحقيقة).
(Trust me.)
(صدقني.)
(Stop working on this.)
(توقف عن العمل على هذا.)
The closer you get to the truth,
كلما اقتربت من الحقيقة ،
the more dangerous it will get.
ستصبح أكثر خطورة.
(Are you sure)
(هل أنت واثق)
(there's nothing wrong with your team?)
(لا يوجد شيء خاطئ مع فريقك؟)
You went in and out of the rehab center as you wish.
لقد دخلت وخرجت من مركز إعادة التأهيل كما يحلو لك.
You moved into the policeman's place
انتقلت إلى مكان الشرطي
and brought the police to the boxing casino to wreck the place.
وأحضرت الشرطة إلى كازينو الملاكمة لتحطيم المكان.
Now, you want to be my business partner.
الآن ، تريد أن تكون شريكي في العمل.
Since I've met you once,
منذ أن قابلتك مرة
I will leave your body intact.
سأترك جسدك سليمًا.
The phone!
الهاتف!
Dong!
دونغ!
It's from the cop!
إنه من الشرطي!
Don't you want to know
لا تريد أن تعرف
how I can go in and out of the Public Security Bureau
كيف يمكنني الدخول والخروج من مكتب الأمن العام
as I wish?
كما أتمنى؟
That's because of the policeman.
هذا بسبب الشرطي.
He is my childhood friend.
إنه صديق طفولتي.
He's with me.
إنه معي.
If you kill me today,
إذا قتلتني اليوم ،
you'll not only upset Mengka
لن تزعج مينكا فقط
but the entire Public Security!
لكن الأمن العام بأكمله!
(Hi.)
(أهلاً.)
(The number you've dialed)
(الرقم الذي طلبته)
(is currently unavailable.)
(غير متوفر حاليا.)
(Please...)
(لو سمحت...)
Do you want to bet?
هل تريد أن الرهان؟
Wu Zhenfeng.
وو تشن فنغ.
Listen.
استمع.
Go back to Mengka now,
ارجع إلى Mengka الآن ،
or I'll do you a favor
أو سأقدم لك معروفا
by sending your dead body back.
عن طريق إعادة جثتك.
Tell Erliang
أخبر إرليانج
that the business has been blown up.
أن العمل قد تم تفجيره.
Kill me if you dare.
اقتلني إذا كنت تجرؤ.
Come back here.
عد إلى هنا.
Come back!
عد!
Wu Zhenfeng.
وو تشن فنغ.
Here's a knife for you.
هنا سكين لك.
You can cut off the rope yourself.
يمكنك قطع الحبل بنفسك.
Jiang Lei.
جيانغ لي.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
Jiang Lei, stay here!
جيانغ لي ، ابق هنا!
Don't leave me.
لا تتركنى.
Don't go!
لا تذهب!
Hao Dong.
هاو دونغ.
Where is Wu Zhenfeng?
أين وو تشن فنغ؟
Where is he?
أين هو؟
Is he dead?
هل هو ميت؟
You...
أنت...
Did you kill another man?
هل قتلت رجلا آخر؟
How are we supposed to keep the business going?
كيف يفترض بنا أن نحافظ على استمرار العمل؟
The police will keep their eyes on us.
سوف تراقب الشرطة أعينها علينا.
You...
أنت...
He's still alive, Mr. Wan.
إنه لا يزال على قيد الحياة ، سيد وان.
Hao Dong.
هاو دونغ.
It's been three years
لقد مرت ثلاث سنوات
since we last dealt with Mengka.
منذ أن تعاملنا آخر مرة مع Mengka.
We can't keep going like this.
لا يمكننا الاستمرار على هذا المنوال.
This is a business.
هذا عمل.
All we want is to make money.
كل ما نريده هو كسب المال.
Peace brings money.
السلام يجلب المال.
Mengka knew that I killed Wu Gang,
عرف مينجكا أنني قتلت وو جانج ،
but they still sent Wu Zhenfeng here
لكنهم ما زالوا يرسلون Wu Zhenfeng هنا
to propose a business deal to me.
لاقتراح صفقة تجارية لي.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
He had no means to smuggle the drugs, right?
لم يكن لديه وسيلة لتهريب المخدرات ، أليس كذلك؟
I'm sure there is too much backlog of goods,
أنا متأكد من وجود الكثير من البضائع المتراكمة ،
right?
الصحيح؟
They were trying to make peace.
كانوا يحاولون صنع السلام.
We can get a 10% more commission
يمكننا الحصول على عمولة أكثر بنسبة 10٪
by providing them with the logistics.
من خلال تزويدهم بالخدمات اللوجستية.
Money, money, and money.
المال والمال والمال.
When it comes to business,
عندما يتعلق الأمر بالأعمال ،
I have the final say.
لدي القول الفصل.
How could you talk to me like that?
كيف يمكنك التحدث معي هكذا؟
Your dad never dared talk to me in this manner
لم يجرؤ والدك على التحدث معي بهذه الطريقة
when he was still around.
عندما كان لا يزال في الجوار.
My dad?
والدي؟
Li Linfan?
لي لينفان؟
You were business partners a few years back.
لقد كنتم شركاء عمل منذ بضع سنوات.
Now, he's dead, but you're still alive.
الآن ، لقد مات ، لكنك ما زلت على قيد الحياة.
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
What's that supposed to mean?
ما الذي يفترض أن يعني؟
When your dad was still around,
عندما كان والدك لا يزال موجودًا ،
all his goods went through the route I picked,
مرت كل بضاعته عبر الطريق الذي اخترته ،
in my vans, and on my boats.
في عرباتي وعلى متن قواربي.
Wu Zhenfeng knows the policeman.
يعرف Wu Zhenfeng الشرطي.
What is their relationship?
ما هي علاقتهم؟
I think they are childhood friends.
أعتقد أنهم أصدقاء الطفولة.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
how did he get released
كيف أطلق سراحه
from the rehab center so soon?
من مركز إعادة التأهيل قريبا جدا؟
The policeman even told someone
حتى أن الشرطي قال لأحدهم
to send him money.
لإرسال المال إليه.
Are you saying
هل تقول
that Wu Zhenfeng works for the police?
أن وو Zhenfeng يعمل للشرطة؟
♪The wind♪
الريح ♪
♪Continues to blow tirelessly♪
♪ يواصل النفخ بلا كلل ♪
♪Above the sky♪
فوق السماء ♪
♪Exists an empty space♪
توجد مساحة فارغة
♪Taking a path♪
اتخاذ مسار ♪
♪Adhering to my original aspiration♪
التمسك بطموحي الأصلي ♪
♪Wounds and pain♪
الجروح والألم ♪
♪Are medals honoring my bravery♪
هي ميداليات تكريم لشجاعي
♪This story♪
♪ هذه القصة ♪
♪It may not be eulogized♪
لا يجوز تأبينه ♪
♪But I remain passionate♪
♪ لكنني ما زلت شغوفًا ♪
♪And willing to give you my all♪
♪ وعلى استعداد لأعطيك كل ما لدي
♪There are always some people♪
♪ هناك دائما بعض الناس
♪Bearing the burden during the peaceful years♪
تحمل العبء في سنوات السلم ♪
♪When breaking out♪
عند الخروج ♪
♪The blazing fire and the raging flame♪
النيران المشتعلة واللهب الهائج
♪Who can see clearly♪
من يستطيع أن يرى بوضوح
♪What I have to bear?♪
♪ ماذا علي أن أتحمل؟ ♪
♪The only way out♪
السبيل الوحيد للخروج
♪Is to burn my bridges♪
هل أحرق جسوري ♪
♪I grit my teeth♪
♪ صرخت أسناني ♪
♪And try to protect you the best I can♪
♪ وحاول أن أحميك بأفضل ما أستطيع
♪Deep down♪
في العمق ♪
♪The past continues and no one has ever changed♪
الماضي مستمر ولم يتغير أحد أبدًا
♪No matter how difficult it is♪
مهما كانت صعوبة
♪Fly over♪
♪ حلق فوق ♪
♪Heaven and Earth♪
السماء والأرض ♪
♪To the end of the world♪
♪ الى نهاية العالم ♪
♪From memories engraved upon my heart♪
من ذكريات محفورة على قلبي ♪
♪I shall be reborn♪
♪ سأولد من جديد ♪
♪I'll never look back♪
♪ لن أنظر إلى الوراء أبدًا ♪
♪And never ask what if♪
♪ ولا تسأل أبدًا ماذا لو ♪
♪Who can see clearly♪
من يستطيع أن يرى بوضوح
♪What I have to bear?♪
♪ ماذا علي أن أتحمل؟ ♪
♪The only way out♪
السبيل الوحيد للخروج
♪Is to burn my bridges♪
هل أحرق جسوري ♪
♪I grit my teeth♪
♪ صرخت أسناني ♪
♪And try to protect you the best I can♪
♪ وحاول أن أحميك بأفضل ما أستطيع
♪Deep down♪
في العمق ♪
♪The past continues and no one has ever changed♪
الماضي مستمر ولم يتغير أحد أبدًا
♪No matter how difficult it is♪
مهما كانت صعوبة
♪Fly over♪
♪ حلق فوق ♪
♪Heaven and Earth♪
السماء والأرض ♪
♪To the end of the world♪
♪ الى نهاية العالم ♪
♪From memories engraved upon my heart♪
من ذكريات محفورة على قلبي ♪
♪I shall be reborn♪
♪ سأولد من جديد ♪
♪I'll never look back♪
♪ لن أنظر إلى الوراء أبدًا ♪
♪And never ask what if♪
♪ ولا تسأل أبدًا ماذا لو ♪